Concept or element that was unfamiliar or unexpected

This was not unexpected but something that I was not familiar with is using GitHub. I work primarily with partner integration 
and have noticed they are starting to migrate more and more towards that to maintain documentation and sdks needed to integrate. I knew this 
was something that I needed to get familiar with but haven't taken the time. This forced me to take a closer look at how to use it, how it
from the other side and the benefits of it which is something that I can take with me and build on whether or not I find employment
at AlsoEnergy.

Constructive review or recommended improvement

I don't know if this was like this because it is an employment challenge or not but that unit test was really long and complex. In my
experience a unit test should only test one thing.

Opportunity or future enhancement

Along the same lines with the above comment, the core classes seem very big and do a lot. I can image that this would be hard to maintain 
and reminds me of something that started out much smaller and more concise and then just grew and grew. If nothing else reorganization with
regions so you can keep like code together, i.e. all import and export stuff in their own region


**Side note that you may or may not find funny but I sure shook my head at it afterwards. I took way to long to figure out the
test bug part. The email said "We recommend starting with the bug fix in the unit test" so I went over and over the test trying to figure
out what was wrong with it. Then I looked at the note in the instructions on the README.md in the repo which said "Fix the bug causing the existing 
unit test to fail" and hung my head in shame.